

Christopher Leonardo de Oliveira FullStack Developer +55 69 99202-9211 christopherforwork@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-de-oliveira/

Description

JavaScript developer with 2 years of student experience, and 1 year active in the industry. High familiarity with React.js, React Native, Redux, Nest.js and Typescript. Explorer and passionate about new adventures, he lived and worked for 1 year in New Zealand to make friends and improve the English language. He works mainly as a freelancer and is looking for a good project to embrace and feel part of. He worked on the *Prismapp* project, and currently develops the *Cashback da Cidade* platform. He is dedicated, communicative, knows how to develop without supervision and also helps colleagues.

Work Experiences

Node Developer

May 2021-July 2021 - **15Segundos**

- 15Segundos App Backend Creator;
- First freelance professional project;
- Use FFMPEG video manipulation library to rotate 9:16 and crop the width of videos in 15 seconds;
- Unfortunately, the project has not yet been launched due to the desire of investors.

FullStack Developer

August 2021-October 2021 - **Betabit Dev**

- PHP programmer, Laravel, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, Vue.js, Flutter;
- He joined as an intern and got 2 promotions in 2 months;
- Worked on the TUDU project, developed by professionals from PUC-PR (the project has a backend in Nest.js, an app in Flutter and a dashboard in React.js);
- https://www.linkedin.com/company/betabit-dev/

December 2021-February 2022 - Prismapp

 Alerts application that sends registered users information about potential risk areas;

- Languages: JavaScript and Typescript;
- Developed with React Native + Redux and Nest.js;
- Makes use of geolocation and Firebase Cloud Messaging;
- https://www.linkedin.com/company/prismapp-brasil/about/

February 2022-now - Cashback da Cidade

- · Cashback app for local merchants;
- Languages: JavaScript and Typescript;
- Developed with React Native + Redux, React.js and Nest.js;
- It makes use of geolocation;
- https://cashbackdacidade.com.br/

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science

Cruzeiro do Sul

Incomplete: 2021 - 2024

Skills

- React Fundamentals (JSX, DOM Virtual, React Native, npm);
- CI/CD and DevOps;
- SCSS, Git;
- Redux;
- Linux;
- English;
- Excellence in communication;
- Team work;
- International experience;

Languages

- JavaScript;
- TypeScript;
- MySQL;